const GAME_DATA = [
    {
        "id": 1,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 27 of ICA",
        "answer": "Agreement in restraint of trade, void"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 14 of ICA",
        "answer": "\"Free consent\" defined"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 16 of ICA",
        "answer": "\"Undue influence\" defined"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 19 of ICA",
        "answer": "Power to set aside contract induced by undue influence"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 11 of ICA",
        "answer": "Who are competent to contract"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 12 of ICA",
        "answer": "What is a sound mind for the purposes of contracting"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 13 of ICA",
        "answer": "\"Consent\" defined"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 15 of ICA",
        "answer": "\"Coercion\" defined"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 17 of ICA",
        "answer": "\"Fraud\" defined"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 18 of ICA",
        "answer": "\"Misrepresentation\" defined"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 20 of ICA",
        "answer": "Agreement void where both parties are under mistake as to matter of fact"
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 21 of ICA",
        "answer": "Effect of mistakes as to law"
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 22 of ICA",
        "answer": "Contract caused by mistake of one party as to matter of fact"
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 23 of ICA",
        "answer": "What considerations and objects are lawful, and what not"
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 24 of ICA",
        "answer": "Agreement void, if considerations and objects unlawful in part"
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 25 of ICA",
        "answer": "Agreement without consideration, void, unless it is in writing and registered, or is a promise to compensate for something done, or is a promise to pay a debt barred by limitation law"
    },
    {
        "id": 17,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 26 of ICA",
        "answer": "Agreement in restraint of marriage, void"
    },
    {
        "id": 18,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 28 of ICA",
        "answer": "Agreements in restraint of legal proceeding void"
    },
    {
        "id": 19,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 29 of ICA",
        "answer": "Agreements void for uncertainty"
    },
    {
        "id": 20,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 30 of ICA",
        "answer": "Agreements by way of wager, void"
    },
    {
        "id": 21,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 31 of ICA",
        "answer": "\"Contingent contract\" defined"
    },
    {
        "id": 22,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 32 of ICA",
        "answer": "Enforcement of contracts contingent on an event happening"
    },
    {
        "id": 23,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 33 of ICA",
        "answer": "Enforcement of contracts contingent on an event not happening"
    },
    {
        "id": 24,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 34 of ICA",
        "answer": "When event on which contract is contingent to be deemed impossible, if it is the future conduct of a living person"
    },
    {
        "id": 25,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 35 of ICA",
        "answer": "When contracts become void which are contingent on happening of specified event within fixed time"
    },
    {
        "id": 26,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 36 of ICA",
        "answer": "Agreement contingent on impossible events void"
    },
    {
        "id": 27,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 37 of ICA",
        "answer": "Obligation of parties to contracts"
    },
    {
        "id": 28,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 38 of ICA",
        "answer": "Effect of refusal to accept offer of performance"
    },
    {
        "id": 29,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 39 of ICA",
        "answer": "Effect of refusal of party to perform promise wholly"
    },
    {
        "id": 30,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 40 of ICA",
        "answer": "Person by whom promise is to be performed"
    },
    {
        "id": 31,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 41 of ICA",
        "answer": "Effect of accepting performance from third person"
    },
    {
        "id": 32,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 42 of ICA",
        "answer": "Devolution of joint liabilities"
    },
    {
        "id": 33,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 43 of ICA",
        "answer": "Any one of joint promisors may be compelled to perform"
    },
    {
        "id": 34,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 44 of ICA",
        "answer": "Effect of release of one joint promisor"
    },
    {
        "id": 35,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 45 of ICA",
        "answer": "Devolution of joint rights"
    },
    {
        "id": 36,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 46 of ICA",
        "answer": "Time for performance of promise, when no application is to be made and no time is specified"
    },
    {
        "id": 37,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 47 of ICA",
        "answer": "Time and place for performance of promise, where time is specified and no application to be made"
    },
    {
        "id": 38,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 48 of ICA",
        "answer": "Application for performance on certain day to be at proper time and place"
    },
    {
        "id": 39,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 49 of ICA",
        "answer": "Place for performance of promise, where no application to be made and no place fixed for performance"
    },
    {
        "id": 40,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 50 of ICA",
        "answer": "Performance in manner or at time prescribed or sanctioned by promisee"
    },
    {
        "id": 41,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 51 of ICA",
        "answer": "Promisor not bound to perform, unless reciprocal promisee ready and willing to perform"
    },
    {
        "id": 42,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 52 of ICA",
        "answer": "Order of performance of reciprocal promises"
    },
    {
        "id": 43,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 53 of ICA",
        "answer": "Liability of party preventing event on which the contract is to take effect"
    },
    {
        "id": 44,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 54 of ICA",
        "answer": "Effect of default as to that promise which should be first performed, in contract consisting of reciprocal promises"
    },
    {
        "id": 45,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 55 of ICA",
        "answer": "Effect of failure to perform at fixed time, in contract in which time is essential"
    },
    {
        "id": 46,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 56 of ICA",
        "answer": "Agreement to do impossible act"
    },
    {
        "id": 47,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 57 of ICA",
        "answer": "Reciprocal promise to do things legal, and also other things illegal"
    },
    {
        "id": 48,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 58 of ICA",
        "answer": "Alternative promise, one branch being illegal"
    },
    {
        "id": 49,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 59 of ICA",
        "answer": "Application of payment where debt to be discharged is indicated"
    },
    {
        "id": 50,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 60 of ICA",
        "answer": "Application of payment where debt to be discharged is not indicated"
    },
    {
        "id": 51,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 61 of ICA",
        "answer": "Application of payment where neither party appropriates"
    },
    {
        "id": 52,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 62 of ICA",
        "answer": "Effect of novation, rescission, and alteration of contract"
    },
    {
        "id": 53,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 63 of ICA",
        "answer": "Promisee may dispense with or remit performance of promise"
    },
    {
        "id": 54,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 64 of ICA",
        "answer": "Consequences of rescission of voidable contract"
    },
    {
        "id": 55,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 65 of ICA",
        "answer": "Obligation of person who has received advantage under void agreement, or contract that becomes void"
    },
    {
        "id": 56,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 66 of ICA",
        "answer": "Mode of communicating or revoking rescission of voidable contract"
    },
    {
        "id": 57,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 67 of ICA",
        "answer": "Effect of neglect of promisee to afford promisor reasonable facilities for performance"
    },
    {
        "id": 58,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 68 of ICA",
        "answer": "Claim for necessaries supplied to person incapable of contracting, or on his account"
    },
    {
        "id": 59,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 69 of ICA",
        "answer": "Reimbursement of person paying money due by another, in payment of which he is interested"
    },
    {
        "id": 60,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 70 of ICA",
        "answer": "Obligation of person enjoying benefit of non-gratuitous act"
    },
    {
        "id": 61,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 72 of ICA",
        "answer": "Liability of person to whom money is paid, or thing delivered, by mistake or under coercion"
    },
    {
        "id": 62,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 73 of ICA",
        "answer": "Compensation for loss or damage caused by breach of contract"
    },
    {
        "id": 63,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 74 of ICA",
        "answer": "Compensation for breach of contract where penalty stipulated for"
    },
    {
        "id": 64,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 75 of ICA",
        "answer": "Party rightfully rescinding contract, entitled to compensation"
    },
    {
        "id": 65,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 1 of ICA",
        "answer": "Short title"
    },
    {
        "id": 66,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 2 of ICA",
        "answer": "Interpretation-clause"
    },
    {
        "id": 67,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 3 of ICA",
        "answer": "Communication, acceptance and revocation of proposals"
    },
    {
        "id": 68,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 4 of ICA",
        "answer": "Communication when complete"
    },
    {
        "id": 69,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 5 of ICA",
        "answer": "Revocation of proposals and acceptances"
    },
    {
        "id": 70,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 6 of ICA",
        "answer": "Revocation how made"
    },
    {
        "id": 71,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 7 of ICA",
        "answer": "Acceptance must be absolute"
    },
    {
        "id": 72,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 8 of ICA",
        "answer": "Acceptance by performing conditions, or receiving consideration"
    },
    {
        "id": 73,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 9 of ICA",
        "answer": "Promises, express and implied"
    },
    {
        "id": 74,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 10 of ICA",
        "answer": "What agreements are contracts"
    },
    {
        "id": 75,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 1 of BNS",
        "answer": "Short title, commencement and application"
    },
    {
        "id": 76,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 2 of BNS",
        "answer": "Definitions."
    },
    {
        "id": 77,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 3 of BNS",
        "answer": "General explanations"
    },
    {
        "id": 78,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 4 of BNS",
        "answer": "Punishments"
    },
    {
        "id": 79,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 5 of BNS",
        "answer": "Commutation of sentence"
    },
    {
        "id": 80,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 6 of BNS",
        "answer": "Fractions of terms of punishment."
    },
    {
        "id": 81,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 7 of BNS",
        "answer": "Sentence may be (in certain cases of imprisonment) wholly or partly rigorous or simple"
    },
    {
        "id": 82,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 8 of BNS",
        "answer": "Amount of fine, liability in default of payment of fine, etc."
    },
    {
        "id": 83,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 9 of BNS",
        "answer": "Limit of punishment of offence made up of several offences."
    },
    {
        "id": 84,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 10 of BNS",
        "answer": "Punishment of person guilty of one of several offences, judgment stating that it is doubtful of which."
    },
    {
        "id": 85,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 11 of BNS",
        "answer": "Solitary confinement."
    },
    {
        "id": 86,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 12 of BNS",
        "answer": "Limit of solitary confinement."
    },
    {
        "id": 87,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 13 of BNS",
        "answer": "Enhanced punishment for certain offences after previous conviction."
    },
    {
        "id": 88,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 14 of BNS",
        "answer": "Act done by a person bound, or by mistake of fact believing himself bound, by law"
    },
    {
        "id": 89,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 15 of BNS",
        "answer": "Act of Judge when acting judicially."
    },
    {
        "id": 90,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 16 of BNS",
        "answer": "Act done pursuant to judgment or order of Court."
    },
    {
        "id": 91,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 17 of BNS",
        "answer": "Act done by a person justified, or by mistake of fact believing himself justified, by law"
    },
    {
        "id": 92,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 18 of BNS",
        "answer": "Accident in doing a lawful act."
    },
    {
        "id": 93,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 19 of BNS",
        "answer": "Act likely to cause harm, but done without criminal intent, and to prevent other harm."
    },
    {
        "id": 94,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 21 of BNS",
        "answer": "Act of a child above seven and under twelve years of age of immature understanding"
    },
    {
        "id": 95,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 22 of BNS",
        "answer": "Act of a person of unsound mind."
    },
    {
        "id": 96,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 23 of BNS",
        "answer": "Act of a person incapable of judgment by reason of intoxication caused against his will"
    },
    {
        "id": 97,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 24 of BNS",
        "answer": "Offence requiring a particular intent or knowledge committed by one who is intoxicated"
    },
    {
        "id": 98,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 25 of BNS",
        "answer": "Act not intended and not known to be likely to cause death or grievous hurt, done by consent."
    },
    {
        "id": 99,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 26 of BNS",
        "answer": "Act not intended to cause death, done by consent in good faith for persons benefit."
    },
    {
        "id": 100,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 27 of BNS",
        "answer": "Act done in good faith for benefit of child or person of unsound mind, by, or by consent of guardian."
    },
    {
        "id": 101,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 28 of BNS",
        "answer": "Consent known to be given under fear or misconception."
    },
    {
        "id": 102,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 29 of BNS",
        "answer": "Exclusion of acts which are offences independently of harm caused."
    },
    {
        "id": 103,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 30 of BNS",
        "answer": "Act done in good faith for benefit of a person without consent."
    },
    {
        "id": 104,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 31 of BNS",
        "answer": "Communication made in good faith."
    },
    {
        "id": 105,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 32 of BNS",
        "answer": "Act to which a person is compelled by threats."
    },
    {
        "id": 106,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 33 of BNS",
        "answer": "Act causing slight harm."
    },
    {
        "id": 107,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 34 of BNS",
        "answer": "Things done in private defence."
    },
    {
        "id": 108,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 35 of BNS",
        "answer": "Right of private defence of body and of property."
    },
    {
        "id": 109,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 36 of BNS",
        "answer": "Right of private defence against act of a person of unsound mind, etc."
    },
    {
        "id": 110,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 37 of BNS",
        "answer": "Acts against which there is no right of private defence."
    },
    {
        "id": 111,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 38 of BNS",
        "answer": "When right of private defence of body extends to causing death."
    },
    {
        "id": 112,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 39 of BNS",
        "answer": "When such right extends to causing any harm other than death."
    },
    {
        "id": 113,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 40 of BNS",
        "answer": "Commencement and continuance of right of private defence of body."
    },
    {
        "id": 114,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 41 of BNS",
        "answer": "When right of private defence of property extends to causing death."
    },
    {
        "id": 115,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 42 of BNS",
        "answer": "When such right extends to causing any harm other than death."
    },
    {
        "id": 116,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 43 of BNS",
        "answer": "Commencement and continuance of right of private defence of property."
    },
    {
        "id": 117,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 44 of BNS",
        "answer": "Right of private defence against deadly assault when there is risk of harm to innocent person."
    },
    {
        "id": 118,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 45 of BNS",
        "answer": "Abetment of a thing."
    },
    {
        "id": 119,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 46 of BNS",
        "answer": "Abettor."
    },
    {
        "id": 120,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 47 of BNS",
        "answer": "Abetment in India of offences outside India."
    },
    {
        "id": 121,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 48 of BNS",
        "answer": "Abetment outside India for offence in India."
    },
    {
        "id": 122,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 49 of BNS",
        "answer": "Punishment of abetment if act abetted is committed in consequence and where no express provision is made for its punishment."
    },
    {
        "id": 123,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 50 of BNS",
        "answer": "Punishment of abetment if person abetted does act with different intention from that of abettor."
    },
    {
        "id": 124,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 51 of BNS",
        "answer": "Liability of abettor when one act abetted and different act done."
    },
    {
        "id": 125,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 52 of BNS",
        "answer": "Abettor when liable to cumulative punishment for act abetted and for act done"
    },
    {
        "id": 126,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 53 of BNS",
        "answer": "Liability of abettor for an effect caused by act abetted different from that intended by abettor."
    },
    {
        "id": 127,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 54 of BNS",
        "answer": "Abettor present when offence is committed."
    },
    {
        "id": 128,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 55 of BNS",
        "answer": "Abetment of offence punishable with death or imprisonment for life."
    },
    {
        "id": 129,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 56 of BNS",
        "answer": "Abetment of offence punishable with imprisonment."
    },
    {
        "id": 130,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 57 of BNS",
        "answer": "Abetting commission of offence by public or by more than ten persons."
    },
    {
        "id": 131,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 58 of BNS",
        "answer": "Concealing design to commit offence punishable with death or imprisonment for life."
    },
    {
        "id": 132,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 59 of BNS",
        "answer": "Public servant concealing design to commit offence which it is his duty to prevent."
    },
    {
        "id": 133,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 60 of BNS",
        "answer": "Concealing design to commit offence punishable with imprisonment."
    },
    {
        "id": 134,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 61 of BNS",
        "answer": "Criminal conspiracy."
    },
    {
        "id": 135,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 62 of BNS",
        "answer": "Punishment for attempting to commit offences punishable with imprisonment for life or other imprisonment."
    },
    {
        "id": 136,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 63 of BNS",
        "answer": "Rape."
    },
    {
        "id": 137,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 64 of BNS",
        "answer": "Punishment for rape."
    },
    {
        "id": 138,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 65 of BNS",
        "answer": "Punishment for rape in certain cases"
    },
    {
        "id": 139,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 66 of BNS",
        "answer": "Punishment for causing death or resulting in persistent vegetative state of victim"
    },
    {
        "id": 140,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 67 of BNS",
        "answer": "Sexual intercourse by husband upon his wife during separation."
    },
    {
        "id": 141,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 68 of BNS",
        "answer": "Sexual intercourse by a person in authority."
    },
    {
        "id": 142,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 69 of BNS",
        "answer": "Sexual intercourse by employing deceitful means, etc."
    },
    {
        "id": 143,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 70 of BNS",
        "answer": "Gang rape."
    },
    {
        "id": 144,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 71 of BNS",
        "answer": "Punishment for repeat offenders."
    },
    {
        "id": 145,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 72 of BNS",
        "answer": "Disclosure of identity of victim of certain offences, etc."
    },
    {
        "id": 146,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 73 of BNS",
        "answer": "Printing or publishing any matter relating to Court proceedings without permission."
    },
    {
        "id": 147,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 74 of BNS",
        "answer": "Assault or use of criminal force to woman with intent to outrage her modesty."
    },
    {
        "id": 148,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 75 of BNS",
        "answer": "Sexual harassment."
    },
    {
        "id": 149,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 76 of BNS",
        "answer": "Assault or use of criminal force to woman with intent to disrobe."
    },
    {
        "id": 150,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 77 of BNS",
        "answer": "Voyeurism."
    },
    {
        "id": 151,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 78 of BNS",
        "answer": "Stalking"
    },
    {
        "id": 152,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 79 of BNS",
        "answer": "Word, gesture or act intended to insult modesty of a woman."
    },
    {
        "id": 153,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 80 of BNS",
        "answer": "Dowry death."
    },
    {
        "id": 154,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 85 of BNS",
        "answer": "Husband or relative of husband of a woman subjecting her to cruelty."
    },
    {
        "id": 155,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 86 of BNS",
        "answer": "Cruelty defined."
    },
    {
        "id": 156,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 100 of BNS",
        "answer": "Culpable homicide."
    },
    {
        "id": 157,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 101 of BNS",
        "answer": "Murder."
    },
    {
        "id": 158,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 102 of BNS",
        "answer": "Culpable homicide by causing death of person other than person whose death was intended."
    },
    {
        "id": 159,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 103 of BNS",
        "answer": "Punishment for murder."
    },
    {
        "id": 160,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 104 of BNS",
        "answer": "Punishment for murder by life-convict"
    },
    {
        "id": 161,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 105 of BNS",
        "answer": "Punishment for culpable homicide not amounting to murder."
    },
    {
        "id": 162,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 106 of BNS",
        "answer": "Causing death by negligence."
    },
    {
        "id": 163,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 107 of BNS",
        "answer": "Abetment of suicide of child or person of unsound mind."
    },
    {
        "id": 164,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 108 of BNS",
        "answer": "Abetment of suicide."
    },
    {
        "id": 165,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 109 of BNS",
        "answer": "Attempt to murder."
    },
    {
        "id": 166,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 110 of BNS",
        "answer": "Attempt to commit culpable homicide."
    },
    {
        "id": 167,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 111 of BNS",
        "answer": "Organised crime."
    },
    {
        "id": 168,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 112 of BNS",
        "answer": "Petty organised crime."
    },
    {
        "id": 169,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 113 of BNS",
        "answer": "Terrorist act."
    },
    {
        "id": 170,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 114 of BNS",
        "answer": "Hurt."
    },
    {
        "id": 171,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 115 of BNS",
        "answer": "Voluntarily causing hurt."
    },
    {
        "id": 172,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 116 of BNS",
        "answer": "Grievous hurt."
    },
    {
        "id": 173,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 117 of BNS",
        "answer": "Voluntarily causing grievous hurt."
    },
    {
        "id": 174,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 118 of BNS",
        "answer": "Voluntarily causing hurt or grievous hurt by dangerous weapons or means."
    },
    {
        "id": 175,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 119 of BNS",
        "answer": "Voluntarily causing hurt or grievous hurt to extort property, or to constrain to an illegal act."
    },
    {
        "id": 176,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 120 of BNS",
        "answer": "Voluntarily causing hurt or grievous hurt to extort confession, or to compel restoration of property."
    },
    {
        "id": 177,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 121 of BNS",
        "answer": "Voluntarily causing hurt or grievous hurt to deter public servant from his duty"
    },
    {
        "id": 178,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 122 of BNS",
        "answer": "Voluntarily causing hurt or grievous hurt on provocation."
    },
    {
        "id": 179,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 123 of BNS",
        "answer": "Causing hurt by means of poison, etc., with intent to commit an offence."
    },
    {
        "id": 180,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 124 of BNS",
        "answer": "Voluntarily causing grievous hurt by use of acid, etc."
    },
    {
        "id": 181,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 125 of BNS",
        "answer": "Act endangering life or personal safety of others."
    },
    {
        "id": 182,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 126 of BNS",
        "answer": "Wrongful restraint."
    },
    {
        "id": 183,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 127 of BNS",
        "answer": "Wrongful confinement."
    },
    {
        "id": 184,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 128 of BNS",
        "answer": "Force."
    },
    {
        "id": 185,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 129 of BNS",
        "answer": "Criminal force."
    },
    {
        "id": 186,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 130 of BNS",
        "answer": "Assault."
    },
    {
        "id": 187,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 131 of BNS",
        "answer": "Punishment for assault or criminal force otherwise than on grave provocation."
    },
    {
        "id": 188,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 132 of BNS",
        "answer": "Assault or criminal force to deter public servant from discharge of his duty."
    },
    {
        "id": 189,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 133 of BNS",
        "answer": "Assault or criminal force with intent to dishonour person, otherwise than on grave provocation."
    },
    {
        "id": 190,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 134 of BNS",
        "answer": "Assault or criminal force in attempt to commit theft of property carried by a person."
    },
    {
        "id": 191,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 135 of BNS",
        "answer": "Assault or criminal force in attempt to wrongfully confine a person."
    },
    {
        "id": 192,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 136 of BNS",
        "answer": "Assault or criminal force on grave provocation."
    },
    {
        "id": 193,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 137 of BNS",
        "answer": "Kidnapping."
    },
    {
        "id": 194,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 138 of BNS",
        "answer": "Abduction."
    },
    {
        "id": 195,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 139 of BNS",
        "answer": "Kidnapping or maiming a child for purposes of begging."
    },
    {
        "id": 196,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 140 of BNS",
        "answer": "Kidnapping or abducting in order to murder or for ransom, etc."
    },
    {
        "id": 197,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 141 of BNS",
        "answer": "Importation of girl or boy from foreign country"
    },
    {
        "id": 198,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 142 of BNS",
        "answer": "Wrongfully concealing or keeping in confinement, kidnapped or abducted person."
    },
    {
        "id": 199,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 143 of BNS",
        "answer": "Trafficking of person."
    },
    {
        "id": 200,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 144 of BNS",
        "answer": "Exploitation of a trafficked person"
    },
    {
        "id": 201,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 145 of BNS",
        "answer": "Habitual dealing in slaves."
    },
    {
        "id": 202,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 146 of BNS",
        "answer": "Unlawful compulsory labour."
    },
    {
        "id": 203,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 147 of BNS",
        "answer": "Waging, or attempting to wage war, or abetting waging of war, against Government of India."
    },
    {
        "id": 204,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 148 of BNS",
        "answer": "Conspiracy to commit offences punishable by section 147."
    },
    {
        "id": 205,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 149 of BNS",
        "answer": "Collecting arms, etc., with intention of waging war against Government of India."
    },
    {
        "id": 206,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 150 of BNS",
        "answer": "Concealing with intent to facilitate design to wage war."
    },
    {
        "id": 207,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 151 of BNS",
        "answer": "Assaulting President, Governor, etc., with intent to compel or restrain exercise of any lawful power."
    },
    {
        "id": 208,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 152 of BNS",
        "answer": "Act endangering sovereignty, unity and integrity of India."
    },
    {
        "id": 209,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 153 of BNS",
        "answer": "Waging war against Government of any foreign State at peace with Government of India."
    },
    {
        "id": 210,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 154 of BNS",
        "answer": "Committing depredation on territories of foreign State at peace with Government of India."
    },
    {
        "id": 211,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 155 of BNS",
        "answer": "Receiving property taken by war or depredation mentioned in sections 153 and 154."
    },
    {
        "id": 212,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 156 of BNS",
        "answer": "Public servant voluntarily allowing prisoner of State or war to escape."
    },
    {
        "id": 213,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 189 of BNS",
        "answer": "Unlawful assembly"
    },
    {
        "id": 214,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 190 of BNS",
        "answer": "Every member of unlawful assembly guilty of offence committed in prosecution of common object."
    },
    {
        "id": 215,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 191 of BNS",
        "answer": "Rioting."
    },
    {
        "id": 216,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 194 of BNS",
        "answer": "Affray."
    },
    {
        "id": 217,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 196 of BNS",
        "answer": "Promoting enmity between different groups on grounds of religion, race, place of birth, residence, language, etc., and doing acts prejudicial to maintenance of harmony"
    },
    {
        "id": 218,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 197 of BNS",
        "answer": "Imputations, assertions prejudicial to national integration."
    },
    {
        "id": 219,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 303 of BNS",
        "answer": "Theft"
    },
    {
        "id": 220,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 304 of BNS",
        "answer": "Snatching"
    },
    {
        "id": 221,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 305 of BNS",
        "answer": "Theft in a dwelling house, or means of transportation or place of worship, etc."
    },
    {
        "id": 222,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 306 of BNS",
        "answer": "Theft by clerk or servant of property in possession of master."
    },
    {
        "id": 223,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 307 of BNS",
        "answer": "Theft after preparation made for causing death, hurt or restraint in order to committing of theft."
    },
    {
        "id": 224,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 308 of BNS",
        "answer": "Extortion."
    },
    {
        "id": 225,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 309 of BNS",
        "answer": "Robbery"
    },
    {
        "id": 226,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 310 of BNS",
        "answer": "Dacoity"
    },
    {
        "id": 227,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 311 of BNS",
        "answer": "Robbery, or dacoity, with attempt to cause death or grievous hurt."
    },
    {
        "id": 228,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 312 of BNS",
        "answer": "Attempt to commit robbery or dacoity when armed with deadly weapon."
    },
    {
        "id": 229,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 313 of BNS",
        "answer": "Punishment for belonging to gang of robbers, etc."
    },
    {
        "id": 230,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 314 of BNS",
        "answer": "Dishonest misappropriation of property."
    },
    {
        "id": 231,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 315 of BNS",
        "answer": "Dishonest misappropriation of property possessed by deceased person at the time of his death."
    },
    {
        "id": 232,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 316 of BNS",
        "answer": "Criminal breach of trust."
    },
    {
        "id": 233,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 317 of BNS",
        "answer": "Stolen property."
    },
    {
        "id": 234,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 318 of BNS",
        "answer": "Cheating"
    },
    {
        "id": 235,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 319 of BNS",
        "answer": "Cheating by personation."
    },
    {
        "id": 236,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 320 of BNS",
        "answer": "Dishonest or fraudulent removal or concealment of property to prevent distribution among creditors."
    },
    {
        "id": 237,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 321 of BNS",
        "answer": "Dishonestly or fraudulently preventing debt being available for creditors."
    },
    {
        "id": 238,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 322 of BNS",
        "answer": "Dishonest or fraudulent execution of deed of transfer containing false statement of consideration."
    },
    {
        "id": 239,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 323 of BNS",
        "answer": "Dishonest or fraudulent removal or concealment of property."
    },
    {
        "id": 240,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 324 of BNS",
        "answer": "Mischief"
    },
    {
        "id": 241,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 325 of BNS",
        "answer": "Mischief by killing or maiming animal."
    },
    {
        "id": 242,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 326 of BNS",
        "answer": "Mischief by injury, inundation, fire or explosive substance, etc."
    },
    {
        "id": 243,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 327 of BNS",
        "answer": "Mischief with intent to destroy or make unsafe a rail, aircraft, decked vessel or one of twenty tons burden."
    },
    {
        "id": 244,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 328 of BNS",
        "answer": "Punishment for intentionally running vessel aground or ashore with intent to commit theft, etc."
    },
    {
        "id": 245,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 329 of BNS",
        "answer": "Criminal trespass and house-trespass."
    },
    {
        "id": 246,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 330 of BNS",
        "answer": "House-trespass and hous-ebreaking."
    },
    {
        "id": 247,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 331 of BNS",
        "answer": "Punishment for house-trespass or house-breaking."
    },
    {
        "id": 248,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 332 of BNS",
        "answer": "House-trespass in order to commit offence."
    },
    {
        "id": 249,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 333 of BNS",
        "answer": "House-trespass after preparation for hurt, assault or wrongful restraint."
    },
    {
        "id": 250,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 334 of BNS",
        "answer": "Dishonestly breaking open receptacle containing property."
    },
    {
        "id": 251,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 356 of BNS",
        "answer": "Defamation"
    },
    {
        "id": 252,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 5 of COI",
        "answer": "Citizenship at the commencement of the Constitution"
    },
    {
        "id": 253,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 6 of COI",
        "answer": "Rights of citizenship of certain persons who have migrated to India from Pakistan"
    },
    {
        "id": 254,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 7 of COI",
        "answer": "Rights of citizenship of certain migrants to Pakistan"
    },
    {
        "id": 255,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 8 of COI",
        "answer": "Rights of citizenship of certain persons of Indian origin residing outside India"
    },
    {
        "id": 256,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 9 of COI",
        "answer": "Persons voluntarily acquiring citizenship of a foreign State not to be citizens"
    },
    {
        "id": 257,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 10 of COI",
        "answer": "Continuance of the rights of citizenship"
    },
    {
        "id": 258,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 11 of COI",
        "answer": "Parliament to regulate the right of citizenship by law"
    },
    {
        "id": 259,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 12 of COI",
        "answer": "Definitions"
    },
    {
        "id": 260,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 13 of COI",
        "answer": "Laws inconsistent with or in derogation of the fundamental rights"
    },
    {
        "id": 261,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 14 of COI",
        "answer": "Equality before law"
    },
    {
        "id": 262,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 15 of COI",
        "answer": "Prohibition of discrimination on grounds of religion, race, caste, sex or place of birth"
    },
    {
        "id": 263,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 16 of COI",
        "answer": "Equality of opportunity in matters of public employment"
    },
    {
        "id": 264,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 17 of COI",
        "answer": "Abolition of Untouchability"
    },
    {
        "id": 265,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 18 of COI",
        "answer": "Abolition of titles"
    },
    {
        "id": 266,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 19 of COI",
        "answer": "Protection of certain rights regarding freedom of speech, etc"
    },
    {
        "id": 267,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 20 of COI",
        "answer": "Protection in respect of conviction for offences"
    },
    {
        "id": 268,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 21 of COI",
        "answer": "Protection of life and personal liberty"
    },
    {
        "id": 269,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 21A of COI",
        "answer": "Right to education"
    },
    {
        "id": 270,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 22 of COI",
        "answer": "Protection against arrest and detention in certain cases"
    },
    {
        "id": 271,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 23 of COI",
        "answer": "Prohibition of traffic in human beings and forced labour"
    },
    {
        "id": 272,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 24 of COI",
        "answer": "Prohibition of employment of children in factories, etc"
    },
    {
        "id": 273,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 25 of COI",
        "answer": "Freedom of conscience and free profession, practice and propagation of religion"
    },
    {
        "id": 274,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 26 of COI",
        "answer": "Freedom to manage religious affairs"
    },
    {
        "id": 275,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 27 of COI",
        "answer": "Freedom as to payment of taxes for promotion of any particular religion"
    },
    {
        "id": 276,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 28 of COI",
        "answer": "Freedom as to attendance at religious instruction or religious worship in certain educational institutions"
    },
    {
        "id": 277,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 29 of COI",
        "answer": "Protection of interests of minorities"
    },
    {
        "id": 278,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 30 of COI",
        "answer": "Right of minorities to establish and administer educational institutions"
    },
    {
        "id": 279,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 31 of COI",
        "answer": "Compulsory acquisition of property"
    },
    {
        "id": 280,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 31A of COI",
        "answer": "Saving of laws providing for acquisition of estates, etc"
    },
    {
        "id": 281,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 31B of COI",
        "answer": "Validation of certain Acts and Regulations"
    },
    {
        "id": 282,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 31C of COI",
        "answer": "Saving of laws giving effect to certain directive principles"
    },
    {
        "id": 283,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 31D of COI",
        "answer": "Saving of laws in respect of anti-national activities"
    },
    {
        "id": 284,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 32 of COI",
        "answer": "Remedies for enforcement of rights conferred by this Part"
    },
    {
        "id": 285,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 32A of COI",
        "answer": "Constitutional validity of State laws not to be considered in proceedings under article 32"
    },
    {
        "id": 286,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 33 of COI",
        "answer": "Power of Parliament to modify the rights conferred by this Part in their application to Forces, etc"
    },
    {
        "id": 287,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 34 of COI",
        "answer": "Restriction on rights conferred by this Part while martial law is in force in any area"
    },
    {
        "id": 288,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 35 of COI",
        "answer": "Legislation to give effect to the provisions of this Part"
    },
    {
        "id": 289,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 36 of COI",
        "answer": "Definition"
    },
    {
        "id": 290,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 37 of COI",
        "answer": "Application of the principles contained in this Part"
    },
    {
        "id": 291,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 38 of COI",
        "answer": "State to secure a social order for the promotion of welfare of the people"
    },
    {
        "id": 292,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 39 of COI",
        "answer": "Certain principles of policy to be followed by the State"
    },
    {
        "id": 293,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 39A of COI",
        "answer": "Equal justice and free legal aid"
    },
    {
        "id": 294,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 40 of COI",
        "answer": "Organisation of village panchayats"
    },
    {
        "id": 295,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 41 of COI",
        "answer": "Right to work, to education and to public assistance in certain cases"
    },
    {
        "id": 296,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 42 of COI",
        "answer": "Provision for just and humane conditions of work and maternity relief"
    },
    {
        "id": 297,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 43 of COI",
        "answer": "Living wage, etc, for workers"
    },
    {
        "id": 298,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 43A of COI",
        "answer": "Participation of workers in management of industries"
    },
    {
        "id": 299,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 44 of COI",
        "answer": "Uniform civil code for the citizens"
    },
    {
        "id": 300,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 45 of COI",
        "answer": "Provision for free and compulsory education for children"
    },
    {
        "id": 301,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 46 of COI",
        "answer": "Promotion of educational and economic interests of Scheduled Castes, Scheduled Tribes and other weaker sections"
    },
    {
        "id": 302,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 47 of COI",
        "answer": "Duty of the State to raise the level of nutrition and the standard of living and to improve public health"
    },
    {
        "id": 303,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 48 of COI",
        "answer": "Organisation of agriculture and animal husbandry"
    },
    {
        "id": 304,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 48A of COI",
        "answer": "Protection and improvement of environment and safeguarding of forests and wild life"
    },
    {
        "id": 305,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 49 of COI",
        "answer": "Protection of monuments and places and objects of national importance"
    },
    {
        "id": 306,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 50 of COI",
        "answer": "Separation of judiciary from executive"
    },
    {
        "id": 307,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 51 of COI",
        "answer": "Promotion of international peace and security"
    },
    {
        "id": 308,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 51A of COI",
        "answer": "Fundamental duties"
    },
    {
        "id": 309,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 226 of COI",
        "answer": "Power of High Courts to issue certain writs"
    },
    {
        "id": 310,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 290A of COI",
        "answer": "Annual payment to certain Devaswom Funds"
    },
    {
        "id": 311,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 1 of COI",
        "answer": "Name and territory of the Union"
    },
    {
        "id": 312,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 2 of COI",
        "answer": "Admission or establishment of new States"
    },
    {
        "id": 313,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 3 of COI",
        "answer": "Formation of new States and alteration of areas, boundaries or names of existing States"
    },
    {
        "id": 314,
        "subject": "Constitutional Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Article",
        "question": "Article 4 of COI",
        "answer": "Laws made under articles 2 and 3 to provide for the amendment of the First and the Fourth Schedules and supplemental, incidental and consequential matters"
    },
    {
        "id": 315,
        "subject": "Criminal Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1",
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 20 of BNS",
        "answer": "Act of a child under seven years of age."
    },
    {
        "id": 316,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 71 of ICA",
        "answer": "Responsibility of finder of goods"
    },
    {
        "id": 317,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 124 of ICA",
        "answer": "\"Contract of indemnity\" defined"
    },
    {
        "id": 318,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 125 of ICA",
        "answer": "Rights of indemnity-holder when sued"
    },
    {
        "id": 319,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 126 of ICA",
        "answer": "\"Contract of guarantee\", \"surety\", \"principal debtor\" and \"creditor\""
    },
    {
        "id": 320,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 127 of ICA",
        "answer": "Consideration for guarantee"
    },
    {
        "id": 321,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 128 of ICA",
        "answer": "Surety\"s liability"
    },
    {
        "id": 322,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 129 of ICA",
        "answer": "\"Continuing guarantee\""
    },
    {
        "id": 323,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 130 of ICA",
        "answer": "Revocation of continuing guarantee"
    },
    {
        "id": 324,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 131 of ICA",
        "answer": "Revocation of continuing guarantee by surety\"s death"
    },
    {
        "id": 325,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 132 of ICA",
        "answer": "Liability of two persons, primarily liable, not affected by arrangement between them that one shall be surety on other\"s default"
    },
    {
        "id": 326,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 133 of ICA",
        "answer": "Discharge of surety by variance in terms of contract"
    },
    {
        "id": 327,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 134 of ICA",
        "answer": "Discharge of surety by release or discharge of principal debtor"
    },
    {
        "id": 328,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 135 of ICA",
        "answer": "Discharge of surety when creditor compounds with, gives time to, or agrees not to sue, principal debtor"
    },
    {
        "id": 329,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 136 of ICA",
        "answer": "Surety not discharged when agreement made with third person to give time to principal debtor"
    },
    {
        "id": 330,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 137 of ICA",
        "answer": "Creditor\"s forbearance to sue does not discharge surety"
    },
    {
        "id": 331,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 138 of ICA",
        "answer": "Release of one co-surety does not discharge others"
    },
    {
        "id": 332,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 139 of ICA",
        "answer": "Discharge of surety of creditor\"s act or omission impairing surety\"s eventual remedy"
    },
    {
        "id": 333,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 140 of ICA",
        "answer": "Rights of surety on payment or performance"
    },
    {
        "id": 334,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 141 of ICA",
        "answer": "Surety\"s right to benefit of creditor\"s securities"
    },
    {
        "id": 335,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 142 of ICA",
        "answer": "Guarantee obtained by misrepresentation invalid"
    },
    {
        "id": 336,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 143 of ICA",
        "answer": "Guarantee obtained by concealment invalid"
    },
    {
        "id": 337,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 144 of ICA",
        "answer": "Guarantee on contract that creditor shall not act on it until co-surety joins"
    },
    {
        "id": 338,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 145 of ICA",
        "answer": "Implied promise to indemnify surety"
    },
    {
        "id": 339,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 146 of ICA",
        "answer": "Co-sureties liable to contribute equally"
    },
    {
        "id": 340,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 147 of ICA",
        "answer": "Liability of co-sureties bound in different sums"
    },
    {
        "id": 341,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 148 of ICA",
        "answer": "\"Bailment\", \"bailor\" and \"bailee\" defined"
    },
    {
        "id": 342,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 149 of ICA",
        "answer": "Delivery to bailee how made"
    },
    {
        "id": 343,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 150 of ICA",
        "answer": "Bailor\"s duty to disclose faults in goods bailed"
    },
    {
        "id": 344,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 151 of ICA",
        "answer": "Care to be taken by bailee"
    },
    {
        "id": 345,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 152 of ICA",
        "answer": "Bailee when not liable for loss, etc, of thing bailed"
    },
    {
        "id": 346,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 153 of ICA",
        "answer": "Termination of bailment by bailee\"s act inconsistent with conditions"
    },
    {
        "id": 347,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 154 of ICA",
        "answer": "Liability of bailee making unauthorized use of goods bailed"
    },
    {
        "id": 348,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 155 of ICA",
        "answer": "Effect of mixture, with bailor\"s consent, of his goods with bailee\"s"
    },
    {
        "id": 349,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 156 of ICA",
        "answer": "Effect of mixture, without bailor\"s consent, when the goods can be separated"
    },
    {
        "id": 350,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 157 of ICA",
        "answer": "Effect of mixture, without bailor\"s consent, when the goods cannot be separated"
    },
    {
        "id": 351,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 158 of ICA",
        "answer": "Repayment, by bailor, of necessary expenses"
    },
    {
        "id": 352,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 159 of ICA",
        "answer": "Restoration of goods lent gratuitously"
    },
    {
        "id": 353,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 160 of ICA",
        "answer": "Return of goods bailed on expiration of time or accomplishment of purpose"
    },
    {
        "id": 354,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 161 of ICA",
        "answer": "Bailee\"s responsibility when goods are not duly returned"
    },
    {
        "id": 355,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 162 of ICA",
        "answer": "Termination of gratuitous bailment by death"
    },
    {
        "id": 356,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 163 of ICA",
        "answer": "Bailor entitled to increase or profit from goods bailed"
    },
    {
        "id": 357,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 164 of ICA",
        "answer": "Bailor\"s responsibility to bailee"
    },
    {
        "id": 358,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 165 of ICA",
        "answer": "Bailment by several joint owners"
    },
    {
        "id": 359,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 166 of ICA",
        "answer": "Bailee not responsible on re-delivery to bailor without title"
    },
    {
        "id": 360,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 167 of ICA",
        "answer": "Right of third person claiming goods bailed"
    },
    {
        "id": 361,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 168 of ICA",
        "answer": "Right of finder of goods"
    },
    {
        "id": 362,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 169 of ICA",
        "answer": "When finder of thing commonly on sale may sell it"
    },
    {
        "id": 363,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 170 of ICA",
        "answer": "Bailee\"s particular lien"
    },
    {
        "id": 364,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 171 of ICA",
        "answer": "General lien of bankers, factors, wharfingers, attorneys and policy-brokers"
    },
    {
        "id": 365,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 172 of ICA",
        "answer": "\"Pledge\", \"Pawnor\" and \"Pawnee\" defined"
    },
    {
        "id": 366,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 173 of ICA",
        "answer": "Pawnee\"s right of retainer"
    },
    {
        "id": 367,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 174 of ICA",
        "answer": "Pawnee not to retain for debt or promise other than that for which goods pledged"
    },
    {
        "id": 368,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 175 of ICA",
        "answer": "Pawnee\"s right as to extraordinary expenses incurred"
    },
    {
        "id": 369,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 176 of ICA",
        "answer": "Pawnee\"s right where pawnor makes default"
    },
    {
        "id": 370,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 177 of ICA",
        "answer": "Defaulting pawnor\"s right to redeem"
    },
    {
        "id": 371,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 178 of ICA",
        "answer": "Pledge by mercantile agent"
    },
    {
        "id": 372,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 178A of ICA",
        "answer": "Pledge by person in possession under voidable contract"
    },
    {
        "id": 373,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 179 of ICA",
        "answer": "Pledge where pawnor has only a limited interest"
    },
    {
        "id": 374,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 180 of ICA",
        "answer": "Suit by bailor or bailee against wrong-doer"
    },
    {
        "id": 375,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 181 of ICA",
        "answer": "Apportionment of relief or compensation obtained by such suits"
    },
    {
        "id": 376,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 182 of ICA",
        "answer": "\"Agent\" and \"principal\" defined"
    },
    {
        "id": 377,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 183 of ICA",
        "answer": "Who may employ agent"
    },
    {
        "id": 378,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 184 of ICA",
        "answer": "Who may be an agent"
    },
    {
        "id": 379,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 185 of ICA",
        "answer": "Consideration not necessary"
    },
    {
        "id": 380,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 186 of ICA",
        "answer": "Agent\"s authority may be expressed or implied"
    },
    {
        "id": 381,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 187 of ICA",
        "answer": "Definitions of express and implied authority"
    },
    {
        "id": 382,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 188 of ICA",
        "answer": "Extent of agent\"s authority"
    },
    {
        "id": 383,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 189 of ICA",
        "answer": "Agent\"s authority in an emergency"
    },
    {
        "id": 384,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 190 of ICA",
        "answer": "When agent cannot delegate"
    },
    {
        "id": 385,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 191 of ICA",
        "answer": "\"Sub-agent\" defined"
    },
    {
        "id": 386,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 192 of ICA",
        "answer": "Representation of principal by sub-agent properly appointed"
    },
    {
        "id": 387,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 193 of ICA",
        "answer": "Agent\"s responsibility for sub-agent appointed without authority"
    },
    {
        "id": 388,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 194 of ICA",
        "answer": "Relation between principal and person duly appointed by agent to act in business of agency"
    },
    {
        "id": 389,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 195 of ICA",
        "answer": "Agent\"s duty in naming such person"
    },
    {
        "id": 390,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 196 of ICA",
        "answer": "Right of person as to acts done for him without his authority"
    },
    {
        "id": 391,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 197 of ICA",
        "answer": "Ratification may be expressed or implied"
    },
    {
        "id": 392,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 198 of ICA",
        "answer": "Knowledge requisite for valid ratification"
    },
    {
        "id": 393,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 199 of ICA",
        "answer": "Effect of ratifying unauthorized act forming part of a transaction"
    },
    {
        "id": 394,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 200 of ICA",
        "answer": "Ratification of unauthorized act cannot injure third person"
    },
    {
        "id": 395,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 201 of ICA",
        "answer": "Termination of agency"
    },
    {
        "id": 396,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 202 of ICA",
        "answer": "Termination of agency, where agent has an interest in subject-matter"
    },
    {
        "id": 397,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 203 of ICA",
        "answer": "When principal may revoke agent\"s authority"
    },
    {
        "id": 398,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 204 of ICA",
        "answer": "Revocation where authority has been partly exercised"
    },
    {
        "id": 399,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 205 of ICA",
        "answer": "Compensation for revocation by principal, or renunciation by agent"
    },
    {
        "id": 400,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 206 of ICA",
        "answer": "Notice of revocation or renunciation"
    },
    {
        "id": 401,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 207 of ICA",
        "answer": "Revocation and renunciation may be expressed or implied"
    },
    {
        "id": 402,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 208 of ICA",
        "answer": "When termination of agent\"s authority takes effect as to agent, and as to third persons"
    },
    {
        "id": 403,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 209 of ICA",
        "answer": "Agent\"s duty on termination of agency by principal\"s death or insanity"
    },
    {
        "id": 404,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 210 of ICA",
        "answer": "Termination of sub-agent\"s authority"
    },
    {
        "id": 405,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 211 of ICA",
        "answer": "Agent\"s duty in conducting principal\"s business"
    },
    {
        "id": 406,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 212 of ICA",
        "answer": "Skill and diligence required from agent"
    },
    {
        "id": 407,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 213 of ICA",
        "answer": "Agent\"s accounts"
    },
    {
        "id": 408,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 214 of ICA",
        "answer": "Agent\"s duty to communicate with principal"
    },
    {
        "id": 409,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 215 of ICA",
        "answer": "Right of principal when agent deals, on his own account, in business of agency without principal\"s consent"
    },
    {
        "id": 410,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 216 of ICA",
        "answer": "Principal\"s right to benefit gained by agent dealing on his own account in business of agency"
    },
    {
        "id": 411,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 217 of ICA",
        "answer": "Agent\"s right of retainer out of sums received on principal\"s account"
    },
    {
        "id": 412,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 218 of ICA",
        "answer": "Agent\"s duty to pay sums received for principal"
    },
    {
        "id": 413,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 219 of ICA",
        "answer": "When agent\"s remuneration becomes due"
    },
    {
        "id": 414,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 220 of ICA",
        "answer": "Agent not entitled to remuneration for business misconducted"
    },
    {
        "id": 415,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 221 of ICA",
        "answer": "Agent\"s lien on principal\"s property"
    },
    {
        "id": 416,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 222 of ICA",
        "answer": "Agent to be indemnified against consequences of lawful acts"
    },
    {
        "id": 417,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 223 of ICA",
        "answer": "Agent to be indemnified against consequences of acts done in good faith"
    },
    {
        "id": 418,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 224 of ICA",
        "answer": "Non-liability of employer of agent to do a criminal act"
    },
    {
        "id": 419,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 225 of ICA",
        "answer": "Compensation to agent for injury caused by principal\"s neglect"
    },
    {
        "id": 420,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 226 of ICA",
        "answer": "Enforcement and consequences of agent\"s contracts"
    },
    {
        "id": 421,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 227 of ICA",
        "answer": "Principal how far bound, when agent exceeds authority"
    },
    {
        "id": 422,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 228 of ICA",
        "answer": "Principal not bound when excess of agent\"s authority is not separable"
    },
    {
        "id": 423,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 229 of ICA",
        "answer": "Consequences of notice given to agent"
    },
    {
        "id": 424,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 230 of ICA",
        "answer": "Agent cannot personally enforce, nor be bound by, contracts on behalf of principal"
    },
    {
        "id": 425,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 231 of ICA",
        "answer": "Rights of parties to a contract made by agent not disclosed"
    },
    {
        "id": 426,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 232 of ICA",
        "answer": "Performance of contract with agent supposed to be principal"
    },
    {
        "id": 427,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 233 of ICA",
        "answer": "Right of person dealing with agent personally liable"
    },
    {
        "id": 428,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 234 of ICA",
        "answer": "Consequence of inducing agent or principal to act on belief that principal or agent will be held exclusively liable"
    },
    {
        "id": 429,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 235 of ICA",
        "answer": "Liability of pretended agent"
    },
    {
        "id": 430,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 236 of ICA",
        "answer": "Person falsely contracting as agent not entitled to performance"
    },
    {
        "id": 431,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 237 of ICA",
        "answer": "Liability of principal inducing belief that agent\"s unauthorized acts were authorized"
    },
    {
        "id": 432,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 2"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 238 of ICA",
        "answer": "Effect, on agreement, of misrepresentation or fraud by agent"
    },
    {
        "id": 433,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 6 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Classes of Criminal Courts"
    },
    {
        "id": 434,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 7 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Territorial divisions."
    },
    {
        "id": 435,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 8 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Court of Session"
    },
    {
        "id": 436,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 9 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Courts of Judicial Magistrates"
    },
    {
        "id": 437,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 10 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Chief Judicial Magistrate and Additional Chief Judicial Magistrate, etc"
    },
    {
        "id": 438,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 11 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Special Judicial Magistrates."
    },
    {
        "id": 439,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 12 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Local Jurisdiction of Judicial Magistrates."
    },
    {
        "id": 440,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 13 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Subordination of Judicial Magistrates"
    },
    {
        "id": 441,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 14 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Executive Magistrates"
    },
    {
        "id": 442,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 15 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Special Executive Magistrates."
    },
    {
        "id": 443,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 16 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Local Jurisdiction of Executive"
    },
    {
        "id": 444,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 17 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Subordination of Executive Magistrates"
    },
    {
        "id": 445,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 18 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Public Prosecutors"
    },
    {
        "id": 446,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 19 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Assistant Public Prosecutors"
    },
    {
        "id": 447,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 20 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Directorate of Prosecution"
    },
    {
        "id": 448,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 21 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Courts by which offences are triable"
    },
    {
        "id": 449,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 22 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Sentences which High Courts and Sessions Judges may pass"
    },
    {
        "id": 450,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 23 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Sentences which Magistrates may pass"
    },
    {
        "id": 451,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 24 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Sentence of imprisonment in default of fine"
    },
    {
        "id": 452,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 25 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Sentence in cases of conviction of several offences at one trial"
    },
    {
        "id": 453,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 26 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Mode of conferring powers"
    },
    {
        "id": 454,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 27 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Powers of officers appointed"
    },
    {
        "id": 455,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 28 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Withdrawal of powers"
    },
    {
        "id": 456,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 29 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Powers of Judges and Magistrates exercisable by their successors-in office"
    },
    {
        "id": 457,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 30 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Powers of superior officers of police"
    },
    {
        "id": 458,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 31 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Public when to assist Magistrates and police"
    },
    {
        "id": 459,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 32 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Aid to person, other than police officer, executing warrant"
    },
    {
        "id": 460,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 33 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Public to give information of certain offences"
    },
    {
        "id": 461,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 34 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Duty of officers employed in connection with affairs of a village to make certain report"
    },
    {
        "id": 462,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 35 of BNSS",
        "answer": "When police may arrest without warrant"
    },
    {
        "id": 463,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 36 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Procedure of arrest and duties of officer making arrest"
    },
    {
        "id": 464,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 37 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Designated police officer"
    },
    {
        "id": 465,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 38 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Right of arrested person to meet an advocate of his choice during interrogation"
    },
    {
        "id": 466,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 39 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Arrest on refusal to give name and residence"
    },
    {
        "id": 467,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 40 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Arrest by private person and procedure on such arrest"
    },
    {
        "id": 468,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 41 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Arrest by Magistrate"
    },
    {
        "id": 469,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 42 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Protection of members of Armed Forces from arrest"
    },
    {
        "id": 470,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 43 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Arrest how made"
    },
    {
        "id": 471,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 44 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Search of place entered by  person sought to be arrested"
    },
    {
        "id": 472,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 45 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Pursuit of offenders into other jurisdictions"
    },
    {
        "id": 473,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 46 of BNSS",
        "answer": "No unnecessary restraint"
    },
    {
        "id": 474,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 47 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Person arrested to be informed of grounds of arrest and of right to bail"
    },
    {
        "id": 475,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 48 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Obligation of person making arrest to inform about arrest, etc., to relative or friend"
    },
    {
        "id": 476,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 49 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Search of arrested person"
    },
    {
        "id": 477,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 50 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power to seize offensive weapons"
    },
    {
        "id": 478,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 51 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Examination of accused by  medical practitioner at  request of  police officer"
    },
    {
        "id": 479,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 52 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Examination of person accused of rape by medical practitioner"
    },
    {
        "id": 480,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 53 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Examination of arrested person by medical officer"
    },
    {
        "id": 481,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 54 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Identification of person arrested"
    },
    {
        "id": 482,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 55 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Procedure when police officer deputes subordinate to arrest without warrant"
    },
    {
        "id": 483,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 56 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Health and safety of arrested person"
    },
    {
        "id": 484,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 57 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Person arrested to be taken before Magistrate or officer in charge of police station"
    },
    {
        "id": 485,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 58 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Person arrested not to be detained more than twenty-four hours"
    },
    {
        "id": 486,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 59 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Police to report apprehensions"
    },
    {
        "id": 487,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 60 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Discharge of person apprehended"
    },
    {
        "id": 488,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 61 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power, on escape, to pursue and retake"
    },
    {
        "id": 489,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 62 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Arrest to be made strictly according to Sanhita"
    },
    {
        "id": 490,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 72 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Form of warrant of arrest and duration"
    },
    {
        "id": 491,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 73 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power to direct security to be taken"
    },
    {
        "id": 492,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 74 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Warrants to whom directed"
    },
    {
        "id": 493,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 75 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Warrant may be directed to any person"
    },
    {
        "id": 494,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 76 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Warrant directed to police officer"
    },
    {
        "id": 495,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 77 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Notification of substance of warrant"
    },
    {
        "id": 496,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 78 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Person arrested to be brought before Court without delay"
    },
    {
        "id": 497,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 79 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Where warrant may be executed"
    },
    {
        "id": 498,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 80 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Warrant forwarded for execution outside jurisdiction"
    },
    {
        "id": 499,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 81 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Warrant directed to police officer for executi on outside jurisdiction"
    },
    {
        "id": 500,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 82 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Procedure on  arrest of person against whom warrant issued"
    },
    {
        "id": 501,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 83 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Procedure by Magistrate before whom such person arrested is brought"
    },
    {
        "id": 502,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 84 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Proclamation for person absconding"
    },
    {
        "id": 503,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 85 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Attachment of property of person absconding"
    },
    {
        "id": 504,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 86 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Identification and attachment of property of proclaimed person"
    },
    {
        "id": 505,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 87 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Claims and objections to attachment"
    },
    {
        "id": 506,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 88 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Release, sale and restoration of attached property"
    },
    {
        "id": 507,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 89 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Appeal from order rejecting application for restoration of attached property"
    },
    {
        "id": 508,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 90 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Issue of warrant in lieu of, or in addition to, summons"
    },
    {
        "id": 509,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 91 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power to take bond or bail bond for appearance"
    },
    {
        "id": 510,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 92 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Arrest on breach of bond or bail bond for appearance"
    },
    {
        "id": 511,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 93 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Provisions of this Chapter generally applicable to summons and warrants of arrest"
    },
    {
        "id": 512,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 94 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Summons to produce document or other thing"
    },
    {
        "id": 513,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 95 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Procedure as to letters"
    },
    {
        "id": 514,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 96 of BNSS",
        "answer": "When search-warrant may be issued"
    },
    {
        "id": 515,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 97 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Search of place suspected to contain stolen property, forged documents, etc"
    },
    {
        "id": 516,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 99 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Application to High Court to set aside declaration of forfeiture"
    },
    {
        "id": 517,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 100 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Search for persons wrongfully confined"
    },
    {
        "id": 518,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 101 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power to compel restoration of abducted femal es"
    },
    {
        "id": 519,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 102 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Direction, etc., of search -warrants"
    },
    {
        "id": 520,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 103 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Persons in charge of closed place to allow search"
    },
    {
        "id": 521,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 104 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Disposal of things found in search beyond jurisdiction"
    },
    {
        "id": 522,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 105 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Recording of search and seizure through audio -video electronic means"
    },
    {
        "id": 523,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 106 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power of police officer to seize certain property"
    },
    {
        "id": 524,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 107 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Attachment, forfeiture or restoration of property"
    },
    {
        "id": 525,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 108 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Magistrate may direct search in his presence"
    },
    {
        "id": 526,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 109 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power to impound document, etc., produced"
    },
    {
        "id": 527,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 110 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Reciprocal arrangements regarding processes"
    },
    {
        "id": 528,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 125 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Security for keeping peace on conviction"
    },
    {
        "id": 529,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 126 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Security for keeping peace in other cases"
    },
    {
        "id": 530,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 127 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Security for good behavio ur from persons disseminating certain matters"
    },
    {
        "id": 531,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 128 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Security for good behaviour from suspected persons"
    },
    {
        "id": 532,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 129 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Security for good behaviour from habitual offenders"
    },
    {
        "id": 533,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 130 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Order to be made"
    },
    {
        "id": 534,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 131 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Procedure in respect of person present in Court"
    },
    {
        "id": 535,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 132 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Summons or warrant in case of person not so present"
    },
    {
        "id": 536,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 133 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Copy of order to accompany summons or warrant"
    },
    {
        "id": 537,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 134 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power to dispense with personal attendance"
    },
    {
        "id": 538,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 135 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Inquiry as to truth of information"
    },
    {
        "id": 539,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 136 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Order to give security"
    },
    {
        "id": 540,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 137 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Discharge of person informed against"
    },
    {
        "id": 541,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 138 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Commencement of period for which security is required"
    },
    {
        "id": 542,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 139 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Contents of bond"
    },
    {
        "id": 543,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 140 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power to reject sureties"
    },
    {
        "id": 544,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 141 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Imprisonment in default of security"
    },
    {
        "id": 545,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 142 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power to release persons imprisoned for failing to give security"
    },
    {
        "id": 546,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 143 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Security for unexpired period of bond"
    },
    {
        "id": 547,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 144 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Order for maintenance of wives, children and parents"
    },
    {
        "id": 548,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 145 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Procedure"
    },
    {
        "id": 549,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 146 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Alteration in allowance"
    },
    {
        "id": 550,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 147 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Enforcement of order of maintenance"
    },
    {
        "id": 551,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 148 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Dispersal of assembly by use of civil force"
    },
    {
        "id": 552,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 149 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Use of armed forces to disperse assembly"
    },
    {
        "id": 553,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 150 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power of ce rtain armed force officers to disperse assembly"
    },
    {
        "id": 554,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 151 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Protection against prosecution for acts done unde r sections 148, 149 and 150"
    },
    {
        "id": 555,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 152 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Conditional order for removal of nuisance"
    },
    {
        "id": 556,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 153 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Service or notification of order"
    },
    {
        "id": 557,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 154 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Person to whom order is addressed to obey or show cause"
    },
    {
        "id": 558,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 155 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Penalty for failure to comply with section 154"
    },
    {
        "id": 559,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 156 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Procedure where existence of public  right is denied"
    },
    {
        "id": 560,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 158 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power of Magistrate to direct local investigation and examination of an expert"
    },
    {
        "id": 561,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 159 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power of Magistrate to furnish written instructions, etc"
    },
    {
        "id": 562,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 160 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Procedure on order being made absolute  and consequences of disobedience"
    },
    {
        "id": 563,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 161 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Injunction pending inquiry"
    },
    {
        "id": 564,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 162 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Magistrate may prohibit repetition or Continuance of public nuisance"
    },
    {
        "id": 565,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 163 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power to issue order in urgent cases of nuisance or apprehended danger"
    },
    {
        "id": 566,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 165 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power to attach subject of dispute and to appoint receiver"
    },
    {
        "id": 567,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 166 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Dispute concerning right of use of land or water"
    },
    {
        "id": 568,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 167 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Local inquiry"
    },
    {
        "id": 569,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 168 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Police to prevent cognizable offences"
    },
    {
        "id": 570,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 169 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Information of design to commit cognizable offences"
    },
    {
        "id": 571,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 170 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Arrest to prevent commission of cognizable offences"
    },
    {
        "id": 572,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 171 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Prevention of injury to public property"
    },
    {
        "id": 573,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 172 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Persons bound to conform to lawful directions of police"
    },
    {
        "id": 574,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 173 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Information in cognizable cases"
    },
    {
        "id": 575,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 174 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Information as to non -cognizable cases and investigation of such cases."
    },
    {
        "id": 576,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 175 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Police officer's power to investigate cognizable case"
    },
    {
        "id": 577,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 176 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Procedure for investigation"
    },
    {
        "id": 578,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 177 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Report how submitted"
    },
    {
        "id": 579,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 178 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power to hold investigation or preliminary inquir y"
    },
    {
        "id": 580,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 179 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Police officers power to require attendance of witnesses"
    },
    {
        "id": 581,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 180 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Examination of witnesses by police"
    },
    {
        "id": 582,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 181 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Statements to police and use thereof"
    },
    {
        "id": 583,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 182 of BNSS",
        "answer": "No inducement to be offered"
    },
    {
        "id": 584,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 183 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Recording of confessions and statements"
    },
    {
        "id": 585,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 184 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Medical examination of victim of rape"
    },
    {
        "id": 586,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 185 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Search by police officer"
    },
    {
        "id": 587,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 186 of BNSS",
        "answer": "When officer in charge of police station may require another to issue search -warrant"
    },
    {
        "id": 588,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 187 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Procedure when investigation cannot be completed in twenty-four hours"
    },
    {
        "id": 589,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 188 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Report of investigation by subordinate police officer"
    },
    {
        "id": 590,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 189 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Release of accused when evidence deficient"
    },
    {
        "id": 591,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 190 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Cases to be sent to Magistrate, when evidence is sufficient"
    },
    {
        "id": 592,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 192 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Diary of proceedings in investigation"
    },
    {
        "id": 593,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 193 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Report of  police officer on completion of investigation"
    },
    {
        "id": 594,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 194 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Police to enquire and report on suicide, etc"
    },
    {
        "id": 595,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 195 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power to summon persons"
    },
    {
        "id": 596,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 196 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Inquiry by Magistrate into cause of death"
    },
    {
        "id": 597,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 197 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Ordinary place of inquiry and trial"
    },
    {
        "id": 598,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 198 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Place of inquiry or trial"
    },
    {
        "id": 599,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 199 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Offence triable where act is done or consequence ensues"
    },
    {
        "id": 600,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 200 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Place of trial where act is an offence by reason of relation to other offence"
    },
    {
        "id": 601,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 201 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Place of trial in case of certain offences"
    },
    {
        "id": 602,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 202 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Offences committed by means of electronic communications, letters, etc"
    },
    {
        "id": 603,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 203 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Offence committed on journey or voyage"
    },
    {
        "id": 604,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 204 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Place of trial for offences triable together"
    },
    {
        "id": 605,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 205 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power to order cases to be tried in diff erent sessions divisions"
    },
    {
        "id": 606,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 206 of BNSS",
        "answer": "High Court to decide, in case of doubt, district w here inquiry or trial shall take place"
    },
    {
        "id": 607,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 207 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power to issue summons or warrant for offence committed beyond local jurisdiction"
    },
    {
        "id": 608,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 208 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Offence committed outside India"
    },
    {
        "id": 609,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 209 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Receipt of evidence relating to offences committed outside India"
    },
    {
        "id": 610,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 210 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Cognizance of offences by Magistrate"
    },
    {
        "id": 611,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 211 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Transfer on application of accused"
    },
    {
        "id": 612,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 212 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Making over of cases to Magistrates"
    },
    {
        "id": 613,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 213 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Cognizance of offences by Court of Session"
    },
    {
        "id": 614,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 214 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Additional Sessions Judges to try cases made over to them"
    },
    {
        "id": 615,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 216 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Procedure for witnesses in case of threatening, etc"
    },
    {
        "id": 616,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 218 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Prosecution of Judges and public servants"
    },
    {
        "id": 617,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 219 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Prosecution for offences against marriage"
    },
    {
        "id": 618,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 220 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Prosecution of offences under section 85 of Bharatiya Nyaya Sanhita, 2023"
    },
    {
        "id": 619,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 221 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Cognizance of offence"
    },
    {
        "id": 620,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 222 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Prosecution for defamation"
    },
    {
        "id": 621,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 223 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Examination of complainant"
    },
    {
        "id": 622,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 224 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Procedure by Magistrate not competent to take cognizance of case"
    },
    {
        "id": 623,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 225 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Postponement of issue of process"
    },
    {
        "id": 624,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 226 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Dismissal of complaint"
    },
    {
        "id": 625,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 227 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Issue of process"
    },
    {
        "id": 626,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 228 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Magistrate may dispense with pe rsonal attendance of accused"
    },
    {
        "id": 627,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 229 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Special summons in cases of petty offence"
    },
    {
        "id": 628,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 230 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Supply to accused of copy of police report and other documents"
    },
    {
        "id": 629,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 232 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Commitment of case to Court of Session when offence is triable exclusively by it"
    },
    {
        "id": 630,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 234 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Contents of charge"
    },
    {
        "id": 631,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 235 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Particulars as to time, place and person"
    },
    {
        "id": 632,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 236 of BNSS",
        "answer": "When manner of committing offence must be stated"
    },
    {
        "id": 633,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 237 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Words in charge taken in sense of law under which offence is punishable"
    },
    {
        "id": 634,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 238 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Effect of errors"
    },
    {
        "id": 635,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 239 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Court may alter charge"
    },
    {
        "id": 636,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 240 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Recall of witnesses when charge altered"
    },
    {
        "id": 637,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 241 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Separate charges for distinct offences"
    },
    {
        "id": 638,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 242 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Offences of same kind within year may be charged together"
    },
    {
        "id": 639,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 243 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Trial for more than one offence"
    },
    {
        "id": 640,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 244 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Where it is doubtful what offence has been committed"
    },
    {
        "id": 641,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 245 of BNSS",
        "answer": "When offence proved included in offence charged"
    },
    {
        "id": 642,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 246 of BNSS",
        "answer": "What persons may be charged jointly"
    },
    {
        "id": 643,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 247 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Withdrawal of remaining charges on conviction on one of several charges"
    },
    {
        "id": 644,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 248 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Trial to be conducted by Public Prosecutor"
    },
    {
        "id": 645,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 249 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Opening case for prosecution"
    },
    {
        "id": 646,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 250 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Discharge"
    },
    {
        "id": 647,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 251 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Framing of charge"
    },
    {
        "id": 648,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 252 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Conviction on plea of guilty"
    },
    {
        "id": 649,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 253 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Date for prosecution evidence"
    },
    {
        "id": 650,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 254 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Evidence for prosecution"
    },
    {
        "id": 651,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 255 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Acquittal"
    },
    {
        "id": 652,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 256 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Entering upon defence"
    },
    {
        "id": 653,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 257 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Arguments"
    },
    {
        "id": 654,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 258 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Judgment of acquittal or conviction"
    },
    {
        "id": 655,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 259 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Previous conviction"
    },
    {
        "id": 656,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 260 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Procedure in cases instituted under sub -section"
    },
    {
        "id": 657,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 261 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Compliance with section 230"
    },
    {
        "id": 658,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 262 of BNSS",
        "answer": "When accused shall be discharged"
    },
    {
        "id": 659,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 263 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Framing of charge"
    },
    {
        "id": 660,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 264 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Conviction on plea of guilty"
    },
    {
        "id": 661,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 265 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Evidence for prosecution"
    },
    {
        "id": 662,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 266 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Evidence for defence"
    },
    {
        "id": 663,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 271 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Acquittal or conviction"
    },
    {
        "id": 664,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 272 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Absence of complainant"
    },
    {
        "id": 665,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 273 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Compensation for accusation without reasonable cause"
    },
    {
        "id": 666,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 274 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Substance of accusation to be stated"
    },
    {
        "id": 667,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 275 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Conviction on plea of guilty"
    },
    {
        "id": 668,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 276 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Conviction on plea of guilty in absence of accused in petty cases"
    },
    {
        "id": 669,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 277 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Procedure when not convicted"
    },
    {
        "id": 670,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 278 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Acquittal or conviction"
    },
    {
        "id": 671,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 279 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Non-appearance or death of complainant"
    },
    {
        "id": 672,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 280 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Withdrawal of complaint"
    },
    {
        "id": 673,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 281 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power to stop proceedings in certain cases"
    },
    {
        "id": 674,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 282 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power of Court to convert summonscases into warrant-cases"
    },
    {
        "id": 675,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 283 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power to try summarily"
    },
    {
        "id": 676,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 284 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Summary trial by Magistrate of second class"
    },
    {
        "id": 677,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 285 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Procedure for summary trials"
    },
    {
        "id": 678,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 286 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Record in summary trials"
    },
    {
        "id": 679,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 287 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Judgment in cases tried summarily"
    },
    {
        "id": 680,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 288 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Language of record and judgment"
    },
    {
        "id": 681,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 289 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Application of Chapter"
    },
    {
        "id": 682,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 290 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Application for plea bargaining"
    },
    {
        "id": 683,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 291 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Guidelines for mutually satisfactory disposition"
    },
    {
        "id": 684,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 292 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Report of mutually satisfactory disposition to be submitted before Court"
    },
    {
        "id": 685,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 293 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Disposal of case"
    },
    {
        "id": 686,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 294 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Judgment of Court"
    },
    {
        "id": 687,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 295 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Finality of judgment"
    },
    {
        "id": 688,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 296 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power of Court in plea bargaining"
    },
    {
        "id": 689,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 297 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Period of detention undergone by accused to be set off against sentence of imprisonment"
    },
    {
        "id": 690,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 298 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Savings"
    },
    {
        "id": 691,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 299 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Statements of accused not to be used"
    },
    {
        "id": 692,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 300 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Non-application of Chapter"
    },
    {
        "id": 693,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 307 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Language of Courts"
    },
    {
        "id": 694,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 308 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Evidence to be taken in presence of accused"
    },
    {
        "id": 695,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 309 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Record in summonscases and inquiries"
    },
    {
        "id": 696,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 310 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Record in warrant -cases"
    },
    {
        "id": 697,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 311 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Record in trial before Court of Session"
    },
    {
        "id": 698,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 312 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Language of record of evidence"
    },
    {
        "id": 699,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 313 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Procedure in regard to such evidence when completed"
    },
    {
        "id": 700,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 314 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Interpretation of evidence to accused or his advocate"
    },
    {
        "id": 701,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 315 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Remarks respecting demeanour of witness"
    },
    {
        "id": 702,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 316 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Record of examination of accused"
    },
    {
        "id": 703,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 317 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Interpreter to be bound to interpret truthfully"
    },
    {
        "id": 704,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 318 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Record in High Court"
    },
    {
        "id": 705,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 319 of BNSS",
        "answer": "When attendance of witness may be dispensed with and commission issued"
    },
    {
        "id": 706,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 320 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Commission to whom to be issued"
    },
    {
        "id": 707,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 321 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Execution of commissions"
    },
    {
        "id": 708,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 322 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Parties may examine witnesses"
    },
    {
        "id": 709,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 323 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Return of commission"
    },
    {
        "id": 710,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 324 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Adjournment of proceeding"
    },
    {
        "id": 711,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 325 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Execution of foreign commissions"
    },
    {
        "id": 712,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 326 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Deposition of medical witness"
    },
    {
        "id": 713,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 327 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Identification report of Magistrate"
    },
    {
        "id": 714,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 328 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Evidence of officers of Mint"
    },
    {
        "id": 715,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 329 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Reports of certain Government scientific experts"
    },
    {
        "id": 716,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 330 of BNSS",
        "answer": "No formal proof of certain documents"
    },
    {
        "id": 717,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 331 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Affidavit in proof of conduct of public servants"
    },
    {
        "id": 718,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 332 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Evidence of formal character on affidavit"
    },
    {
        "id": 719,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 333 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Authorities before whom affidavits may be sworn"
    },
    {
        "id": 720,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 334 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Previous conviction or acquittal how proved"
    },
    {
        "id": 721,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 335 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Record of evidence  in absence of accused"
    },
    {
        "id": 722,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 336 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Evidence of public servants, experts, police officers in certain cases"
    },
    {
        "id": 723,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 337 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Person once convicted or acquitted not to be tried for same offence"
    },
    {
        "id": 724,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 340 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Right of person  against whom proceedings are instituted to be defended"
    },
    {
        "id": 725,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 341 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Legal aid to accused at State expense in certain cases"
    },
    {
        "id": 726,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 344 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power to direct tender of pardon"
    },
    {
        "id": 727,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 345 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Trial of person not complying with conditions of pardon"
    },
    {
        "id": 728,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 359 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Compounding of offences"
    },
    {
        "id": 729,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 360 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Withdrawal from prosecution"
    },
    {
        "id": 730,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 367 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Procedure in case of accused being person of unsound mind"
    },
    {
        "id": 731,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 368 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Procedure in case of person of unsound mind tried before Court"
    },
    {
        "id": 732,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 369 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Release of person of unsound mind pending investigation or trial"
    },
    {
        "id": 733,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 370 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Resumption of inquiry or trial"
    },
    {
        "id": 734,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 371 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Procedure on accused appearing before Magistrate or Court"
    },
    {
        "id": 735,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 372 of BNSS",
        "answer": "When accused appears to have been of sound mind"
    },
    {
        "id": 736,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 373 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Judgment of acquittal on ground of unsoundness of mind"
    },
    {
        "id": 737,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 374 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Person acquitted on ground of unsoundness of mind to be detained in safe custody"
    },
    {
        "id": 738,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 375 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power of State Government to empower officer in charge to discharge"
    },
    {
        "id": 739,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 376 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Procedure where prisoner of unsound mind is reported capable of making his defence"
    },
    {
        "id": 740,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 377 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Procedure where person of unsound mind detained is declared fit to be released"
    },
    {
        "id": 741,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 378 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Delivery of person of unsound mind to care of relative or friend"
    },
    {
        "id": 742,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 407 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Sentence of death to be submitted by Court of Session for confirmation"
    },
    {
        "id": 743,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 408 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power to direct further inquiry to be made or additional evidence to be taken"
    },
    {
        "id": 744,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 409 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power of High Court to confirm sentence or annul conviction"
    },
    {
        "id": 745,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 410 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Confirmation or new sentence to be signed by two Judges"
    },
    {
        "id": 746,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 411 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Procedure in case of difference of opinion"
    },
    {
        "id": 747,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 412 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Procedure in cases submitted to High Court for confirmation"
    },
    {
        "id": 748,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 413 of BNSS",
        "answer": "No appeal to lie unless otherwise provided"
    },
    {
        "id": 749,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 415 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Appeals from convictions"
    },
    {
        "id": 750,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 416 of BNSS",
        "answer": "No appeal in certain cases when accused pleads guilty"
    },
    {
        "id": 751,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 417 of BNSS",
        "answer": "No appeal in petty cases"
    },
    {
        "id": 752,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 418 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Appeal by State Government against sentence"
    },
    {
        "id": 753,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 419 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Appeal in case of acquittal"
    },
    {
        "id": 754,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 420 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Appeal against conviction by High C ourt in certain cases"
    },
    {
        "id": 755,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 421 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Special right of appeal in certain cases"
    },
    {
        "id": 756,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 422 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Appeal to Court of Session how heard"
    },
    {
        "id": 757,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 423 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Petition of appeal"
    },
    {
        "id": 758,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 424 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Procedure when appellant in jail"
    },
    {
        "id": 759,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 425 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Summary dismissal of appeal"
    },
    {
        "id": 760,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 426 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Procedure for hearing appeals not dismissed summarily"
    },
    {
        "id": 761,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 427 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Powers of Appellate Court"
    },
    {
        "id": 762,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 428 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Judgments of subordinate Appellate Court"
    },
    {
        "id": 763,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 429 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Order of High Court on appeal to be certified to lower Court"
    },
    {
        "id": 764,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 430 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Suspension of sentence pending appeal; release of appellant on bail"
    },
    {
        "id": 765,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 431 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Arrest of accused in appeal from acquittal"
    },
    {
        "id": 766,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 432 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Appellate Court may take further evidence or direct it to be taken"
    },
    {
        "id": 767,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 433 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Procedure where Judges of Court of appeal are equally divided"
    },
    {
        "id": 768,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 434 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Finality of judgments and orders on appeal"
    },
    {
        "id": 769,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 435 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Abatement of appeals"
    },
    {
        "id": 770,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 436 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Reference to High Court"
    },
    {
        "id": 771,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 437 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Disposal of case according to decision of High Court"
    },
    {
        "id": 772,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 438 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Calling for records to exercise powers of revision"
    },
    {
        "id": 773,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 439 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power to order inquiry"
    },
    {
        "id": 774,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 440 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Sessions Judges powers of revision"
    },
    {
        "id": 775,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 441 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power of Additional Sessions Judge"
    },
    {
        "id": 776,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 442 of BNSS",
        "answer": "High Courts powers of revision"
    },
    {
        "id": 777,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 443 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power of High Court to withdraw or transfer revision cases"
    },
    {
        "id": 778,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 444 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Option of Court to hear parties"
    },
    {
        "id": 779,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 445 of BNSS",
        "answer": "High Courts order to be certified to lower Court"
    },
    {
        "id": 780,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 446 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power of Supreme Court to transfer cases and appeals"
    },
    {
        "id": 781,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 447 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power of High Court to transfer cases and appeals"
    },
    {
        "id": 782,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 448 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power of Sessions Judge to transfer cases and appeals"
    },
    {
        "id": 783,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 449 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Withdrawal of cases and appeals by Sessions Judges"
    },
    {
        "id": 784,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 450 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Withdrawal of cases by Judicial Magi strates"
    },
    {
        "id": 785,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 451 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Making over or withdrawal of cases by Executive Magistrates"
    },
    {
        "id": 786,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 452 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Reasons to be recorded"
    },
    {
        "id": 787,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 453 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Execution of order passed under section 409"
    },
    {
        "id": 788,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 454 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Execution of sentence of death passed by High Court"
    },
    {
        "id": 789,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 456 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Commutation of sentence of death on pregnant woman"
    },
    {
        "id": 790,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 457 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power to appoint place of imprisonment"
    },
    {
        "id": 791,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 458 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Execution of sentence of imprisonment"
    },
    {
        "id": 792,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 459 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Direction of warrant for execution"
    },
    {
        "id": 793,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 460 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Warrant with whom to be lodged"
    },
    {
        "id": 794,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 461 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Warrant for levy of fine"
    },
    {
        "id": 795,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 462 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Effect of such warrant"
    },
    {
        "id": 796,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 464 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Suspension of execution of sentence of imprisonment"
    },
    {
        "id": 797,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 465 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Who may issue warrant"
    },
    {
        "id": 798,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 466 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Sentence on escaped convict when to take effect"
    },
    {
        "id": 799,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 467 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Sentence on offender already sentenced  for another offence"
    },
    {
        "id": 800,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 468 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Period of detention undergone by accused to be set off against sentence of imprisonment"
    },
    {
        "id": 801,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 469 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Saving"
    },
    {
        "id": 802,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 470 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Return of warrant on execution of sentence"
    },
    {
        "id": 803,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 471 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Money ordered to be paid recoverable as a fine"
    },
    {
        "id": 804,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 472 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Mercy petition in death sentence cases"
    },
    {
        "id": 805,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 473 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power to suspend or remit sentences"
    },
    {
        "id": 806,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 474 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power to commute sentence"
    },
    {
        "id": 807,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 475 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Restriction on powers of remission or commutation in certain cases"
    },
    {
        "id": 808,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 476 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Concurrent power of Central Government in case of death sentences"
    },
    {
        "id": 809,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 477 of BNSS",
        "answer": "State Government to act after concurrence with Central Government in certain cases"
    },
    {
        "id": 810,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 478 of BNSS",
        "answer": "In what cases bail to be taken"
    },
    {
        "id": 811,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 479 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Maximum period for which under  trial prisoner can be detained"
    },
    {
        "id": 812,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 480 of BNSS",
        "answer": "When bail may be taken in case of non-bailable offence"
    },
    {
        "id": 813,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 481 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Bail to require accused to appear before next Appellate Court"
    },
    {
        "id": 814,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 482 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Direction for grant of bail to person apprehending arrest"
    },
    {
        "id": 815,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 483 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Special powers of High Court or Court of Session regarding bail"
    },
    {
        "id": 816,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 484 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Amount of bond and reduction thereof"
    },
    {
        "id": 817,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 485 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Bond of accused and sureties"
    },
    {
        "id": 818,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 486 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Declaration by sureties"
    },
    {
        "id": 819,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 487 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Discharge from custody"
    },
    {
        "id": 820,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 488 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power to order sufficient bail when that first taken is insufficient"
    },
    {
        "id": 821,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 489 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Discharge of sureties"
    },
    {
        "id": 822,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 490 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Deposit instead of recognizance"
    },
    {
        "id": 823,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 491 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Procedure when bond has been forfeited"
    },
    {
        "id": 824,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 492 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Cancellation of bond and bail bond"
    },
    {
        "id": 825,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 493 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Procedure in case of insolvency or death of surety or when a bond is forfeited"
    },
    {
        "id": 826,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 494 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Bond required from child"
    },
    {
        "id": 827,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 495 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Appeal from orders under section 491"
    },
    {
        "id": 828,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 496 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Power to direct levy of amount due on c ertain recognizances"
    },
    {
        "id": 829,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 506 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Irregularities which do not vitiate proceedings"
    },
    {
        "id": 830,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 507 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Irregularities which vitiate proceedings"
    },
    {
        "id": 831,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 508 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Proceedings in wrong place"
    },
    {
        "id": 832,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 509 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Non-compliance with provisions of section 183 or section 316"
    },
    {
        "id": 833,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 510 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Effect of omission to frame, or absence of, or error in, charge"
    },
    {
        "id": 834,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 511 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Finding or sentence when reversible by reason of error, omission or irregularity"
    },
    {
        "id": 835,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 512 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Defect or error not to make attachment unlawful"
    },
    {
        "id": 836,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 513 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Definitions"
    },
    {
        "id": 837,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 514 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Bar to taking cognizance after lapse of period of limitation"
    },
    {
        "id": 838,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 515 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Commencement of period of limitation"
    },
    {
        "id": 839,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 516 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Exclusion of time in certai n cases"
    },
    {
        "id": 840,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 517 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Exclusion of date on which Court is closed"
    },
    {
        "id": 841,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 518 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Continuing offence"
    },
    {
        "id": 842,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 519 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Extension of period of limitation in certain cases"
    },
    {
        "id": 843,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 520 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Trials before High Courts"
    },
    {
        "id": 844,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 525 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Cases in which Judge or Magistrate is personally interested"
    },
    {
        "id": 845,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 526 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Practising advocate not to sit as Magistrate in certain Courts"
    },
    {
        "id": 846,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 527 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Public servant concerned in sale not to purchase or bid for property"
    },
    {
        "id": 847,
        "subject": "Criminal Procedure Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 3"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 528 of BNSS",
        "answer": "Saving of inherent powers of High Court"
    },
    {
        "id": 848,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 10 of SRA",
        "answer": "Specific performance in respect of contracts"
    },
    {
        "id": 849,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 11 of SRA",
        "answer": "Cases in which specific performance of contracts connected with trusts enforceable"
    },
    {
        "id": 850,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 12 of SRA",
        "answer": "Specific performance of part of contract"
    },
    {
        "id": 851,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 13 of SRA",
        "answer": "Rights of purchaser or lessee against person with no title or imperfect title"
    },
    {
        "id": 852,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 14 of SRA",
        "answer": "Contracts not specifically enforceable"
    },
    {
        "id": 853,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 15 of SRA",
        "answer": "Who may obtain specific performance"
    },
    {
        "id": 854,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 16 of SRA",
        "answer": "Personal bars to relief"
    },
    {
        "id": 855,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 19 of SRA",
        "answer": "Relief against parties and persons claiming under them by subsequent title"
    },
    {
        "id": 856,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 20 of SRA",
        "answer": "Substituted performance of contract"
    },
    {
        "id": 857,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 21 of SRA",
        "answer": "Power to award compensation in certain cases"
    },
    {
        "id": 858,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 22 of SRA",
        "answer": "Power to grant relief for possession, partition, refund of earnest money, etc"
    },
    {
        "id": 859,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 23 of SRA",
        "answer": "Liquidation of damages not a bar to specific performance"
    },
    {
        "id": 860,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 24 of SRA",
        "answer": "Bar of suit for compensation for breach after dismissal of suit for specific performance"
    },
    {
        "id": 861,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 26 of SRA",
        "answer": "When instrument may be rectified"
    },
    {
        "id": 862,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 27 of SRA",
        "answer": "When rescission may be adjudged or refused"
    },
    {
        "id": 863,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 28 of SRA",
        "answer": "Rescission in certain circumstances of contracts for the sale or lease of immovable property, the specific performance of which has been decreed"
    },
    {
        "id": 864,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 29 of SRA",
        "answer": "Alternative prayer for rescission in suit for specific performance"
    },
    {
        "id": 865,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 30 of SRA",
        "answer": "Court may require parties rescinding to do equity"
    },
    {
        "id": 866,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 31 of SRA",
        "answer": "When cancellation may be ordered"
    },
    {
        "id": 867,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 33 of SRA",
        "answer": "Power to require benefit to be restored or compensation to be made when instrument is cancelled or is successfully resisted as being void or voidable"
    },
    {
        "id": 868,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 36 of SRA",
        "answer": "Preventive relief how granted"
    },
    {
        "id": 869,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 37 of SRA",
        "answer": "Temporary and perpetual injunctions"
    },
    {
        "id": 870,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 38 of SRA",
        "answer": "Perpetual injunction when granted"
    },
    {
        "id": 871,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 39 of SRA",
        "answer": "Mandatory injunctions"
    },
    {
        "id": 872,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 40 of SRA",
        "answer": "Damages in lieu of, or in addition to, injunction"
    },
    {
        "id": 873,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 41 of SRA",
        "answer": "Injunction when refused"
    },
    {
        "id": 874,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 42 of SRA",
        "answer": "Injunction to perform negative agreement"
    },
    {
        "id": 875,
        "subject": "Contract Law",
        "semester": [
            "Sem 1"
        ],
        "type": "Section",
        "question": "Section 9 of SRA",
        "answer": "Defences respecting suits for relief based on contract"
    }
];